Last year, we held a special
Spread the Health fundraiser
to provide free copies of our
Evidence-Based Eating Guide
to health care practitioners
across the United States.
Thanks to your support,
we were able to send out
12,000 copies
to those who counsel
individuals on healthy eating
so they could distribute them
to their clients and patients.
Now we want to make it out to
even more people with your help.
Please consider helping us
send even more copies
of this important resource to
health care practitioners in 2023.
With increased publishing
and shipping costs,
we’d be even more
grateful for your help
in getting them directly into
the hands of practitioners.
Just $20 allows us to
print and ship about 16 copies
of the Evidence-Based Eating Guide
to doctor’s offices,
hospitals, and health clinics.
Please consider making
a donation today
to help us spread the health!
Thank you for your support.